Guide to the UE National Office Records Relating to District 7 and District 7 Locals, 1936-1997 UE.4.1.7
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- District 7 Locals, 2.
  - Local 703
    - Local 703 Incoming Correspondence, September 21, 1939-December 5, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 54)
      - Emspak to Patton Regarding Protest, June 4, 1947; 24.
      - Emspak to Frank Greene Regarding Finances, December 5, 1950; 25.
    - Local 703 Incoming Correspondence, August 13, 1941-March 23, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 55)
      - Julius Emspak to Vern Slagle Regarding Amalgamation, November 26, 1951; 1.
      - Emspak to Stephen Hendl Regarding Change of Local, December 21, 1951; 2.
      - Emspak to Hendl Regarding Publications, December 12, 1951; 3.
      - Emspak to Hendl Regarding Local Change, February 20, 1952; 4.
      - Emspak to Ray Woth Regarding Strike Finances, December 1, 1952; 5.
      - Emspak to Harold Richards Regarding Finances, January 27, 1956; 6.
      - Emspak to Claude Logan Regarding Address Change, February 2, 1956; 7.
      - Emspak to Richards Regarding Strike Finances, February 15, 1956; 8.
      - Emspak to Richards Regarding Strike Finances, March 23, 1956; 9.
      - Emspak to Richards Regarding Strike Finances, February 24, 1956; 10.
      - Albert Fitzgerald to Edward Rothermel Regarding Acknowledged Letter, June 1, 1943; 11.
      - Nat Geller to Carl Bennett Regarding Finances, October 12, 1942; 12.
      - James Matles to John Horvath Regarding Negiotiations, August 13, 1941; 13.
      - Matles to J. Patton Regarding Strike Victory, August 15, 1946; 14.
      - J. Smith to Patton Regarding Work Stoppage, February 28, 1946; 15.
    - Local 703 Outgoing Correspondence, October 4, 1937-October 21, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 56)
      - Carl Bennett to Julius Emspak Regarding Local Constitution, October 7, 1942; 1.
      - Bennett to Emspak Regarding Materials, October 14, 1942; 2.
      - Bennett to Nat Geller Regarding Printing Order, October 21, 1942; 3.
      - Bennett to Emspak Regarding Address, November 5, 1942; 4.
      - Bennett to Emspak Regarding Steward System, April 26, 1943; 5.
      - Bennett to James Byrnes Regarding Executive Order, April 20, 1943; 6.
      - Bennett to Emspak Regarding Resolution, May 19, 1943; 7.
      - A. Drumm to Emspak Regarding Information Request, October 4, 1937; 8.
      - Mike Dudock to Emspak Regarding Strike Fund, June 12, 1946; 9.
      - Dudock to Emspak Regarding Strike Fund, July 5, 1946; 10.
      - Executive Board to Harry Truman Regarding Florida Bombings, January 14, 1952; 11.
      - Executive Board to John Bicker Regarding Investigation Request, January 14, 1952; 12.
      - Executive Board to Robert Taft Regarding Investigation Request, January 14, 1952; 13.
      - Executive Board to Representitive Bender Regarding Investigation Request, January 14, 1952; 14.
      - Executive Board to William Ayres Regarding Investigation Request, January 14, 1952; 15.
      - Executive Board to Herman Talmmage Regarding Investigation Request, January 14, 1952; 16.
      - Executive Board to Taft Regarding Protection of Rights, January 15, 1952; 17.
      - Executive Board to Bricker Regarding Protection of Rights, January 15, 1942; 18.
      - Executive Board to Ayres Regarding Protection of Rights, January 15, 1942; 19.
      - Frank Greene to Emspak Regarding Finances, April 1, 1950; 20.
      - Greene to Emspak Regarding IUE Workers, April 22, 1950; 21.
      - Greene to Emspak Regarding News Items, April 23, 1951; 22.
      - Greene to Emspak Regarding Strike Finances, October 21, 1952; 23.
      - Stephen Hendl to Emspak Regarding Amalgamation, December 8, 1951; 24.
      - Hendl to Emspak Regarding Pay Cuts, December 8, 1951; 25.
      - Hendl to Emspak Regarding Letter Copies, February 9, 1952; 26.
    - Local 703 Outgoing Correspondence, September 5, 1939-February 9, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 57)
      - John Horvath to President Roosevelt Regarding Protest Against Troops, June 11, 1941; 1.
      - Horvath to Julius Emspak Regarding Contract, August 11, 1941; 2.
      - Horvath to James Matles Regarding Contract, October 5, 1941; 3.
      - Horvath to Emspak Regarding Wage Increases, January 14, 1942; 4.
      - Horvath to Emspak Regarding Finances, February 25, 1942; 5.
      - Victor Lyons to Emspak Regarding Credentials, March 15, 1944; 6.
      - Lyons to Emspak Regarding Finances, January 22, 1946; 7.
      - Lyons to Emspak Regarding Cases in Question, January 24, 1946; 8.
      - Lyons to Emspak Regarding Credentials, January 24, 1946; 9.
      - Paul Mavrides to Emspak Regarding Local Affairs, January 24, 1946; 10.
      - J. Patton to Mr. Schwellenbach Regarding Pending Strike, November 23, 1945; 11.
      - Patton Letter Regarding Enclosed Information, December 3, 1945; 12.
      - Patton to Emspak Regarding Strike, June 5, 1946; 13.
      - Patton to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Strike End, August 13, 1946; 14.
      - Patton to Fitzgerald Regarding Strike End, August 18, 1946; 15.
      - Patton to Emspak Regarding Protests, June 4, 1947; 16.
      - Patton to Emspak Regarding Strike, 17.
      - Harold Richards to Emspak Regarding Strike Fund, January 30, 1956; 18.
      - Richards to Emspak Regarding Strike Finances, February 9, 1956; 19.
      - Richards to Emspak Regarding Strike Finances, January 18, 1956; 20.
      - Edward Rothermel to Emspak Regarding Executive Committee, May 20, 1943; 21.
      - Albert Soden to Emspak Regarding Supplies, September 5, 1939; 22.
      - Joseph Wright to Emspak Regarding Finances, January 2, 1951; 23.
    - Local 703 Akron Imperial Electric, August 13, 1936-December 23, 1937 (Box 4, Folder 58)
    - Local 703 Legislative Committee and Political Action, April 15, 1971-August 14, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 59)
    - Local 703 Akron Imperial Electric, August 14, 1937-August 26, 1938 (Box 4, Folder 60)
    - Local 703 Financial Requesitions, August 14, 1939-January 29, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 61)
    - Local 703 Pamphlets, 1937 (Box 4, Folder 62)
    - Local 703 Company UE News Subs, February 10-March 1, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 63)
      - Julius Emspak to John Harty, February 10, 1941; 1.
      - Hearty to Emspak, March 7, 1941; 2.
    - Local 703 Strike, November 30, 1945-March 20, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 64)
      - Notification of Pending Disagreement, November 30, 1945; 1.
      - J.K. Smith to J.C. Patton, February 28, 1946; 2.
      - Smith to Albert Fitzgerald, February 28, 1946; 3.
      - Fitzgerald to Herbert Hirshberg, March 6, 1946; 4.
      - Fitzgerald to Smith, March 6, 1946; 5.
      - Notification of Pending Disagreement, March 1946; 6.
      - Joseph Icres to Fitzgerald, March 14, 1946; 7.
      - Report of Strike, March 20, 1946; 8.
    - Local 703 Correspondence and Report, September 18, 1942-October 31, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 65)
      - Joseph Vejlupek to John Hearty Regarding War Production, September 18, 1942; 1.
      - Frank Mance to James Matles Regarding Collective Barganing, November 16, 1942; 2.
      - Excerpt of Report to Vern Slagle Regarding Stockwell Transformer Organization, October 16-31, 1951; 3.
  - Local 704 (Cuyahoga Falls)
    - Local 704 (Cuyahoga Falls) Constitution and By-Laws (Box 4, Folder 66)
    - Local 704 (Cuyahoga Falls) Constitution, July 9, 1947-March 1, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 67)
    - Local 704 (Cuyahoga Falls) Membership List (Box 4, Folder 68)
    - Local 704 (Cuyahoga Falls) Incoming Correspondence, Spetember 24, 1936-May 19, 1937 (Box 4, Folder 69)
      - Janet Barish to R.T. Hartley Regarding Supplies, December 12, 1936; 1.
      - Barish to Hartley Regarding Mailing Addresses, December 23, 1936; 2.
      - Barish to Hartley Regarding Membership, January 5, 1937; 3.
      - Barish to F. Herdmen Regarding Supplies, January 9, 1937; 4.
      - Barish to Herdman Regarding Supplies, February 9, 1937; 5.
      - Barish to Herdman Regarding Finances, March 17, 1937; 6.
      - Barish to Hartley Regarding Finances, March 25, 1937; 7.
      - Barish to Hartley Regarding Convention, April 23, 1937; 8.
      - Barish to Herdman Regarding Finances, May 19, 1937; 9.
      - Julius Emspak to Walter Barringer Regarding Finances, September 24, 1936; 10.
      - Emspak to Barringer Regarding Finances, September 25, 1936; 11.
      - Emspak to Barringer Regarding Supplies, September 25, 1936; 12.
      - Emspak to Herdman Regarding Finances, October 14, 1936; 13.
      - Emspak to Herdman Regarding Supplies, November 16, 1936; 14.
      - Emspak to Herdman Regarding Supplies, October 28, 1936; 15.
      - Emspak to Hartley Regarding Supplies, October 28, 1936; 16.
      - Emspak to Hartley Regarding Supplies, November 11, 1936; 17.
      - Emspak to Herdman Regarding Supplies, November 11, 1936; 18.
      - Emspak to Hartley Regarding Supplies, November 17, 1936; 19.
      - Emspak to Herdman Regarding Finances, November 18, 1936; 20.
      - Emspak to Herdman Regarding Supplies, November 20, 1936; 21.
      - Emspak to Hartley Regarding Finances, December 1, 1936; 22.
      - Emspak to Herdman Regarding Finances, Decembe 12, 1936; 23.
      - Emspak to Hartley Regarding Union Affiliation, December 19, 1936; 24.
      - Emspak to Hartley Regarding Local Organization, December 30, 1936; 25.
    - Local 704 (Cuyahoga Falls) Incoming Correspondence, January 8, 1937-January 17, 1938 (Box 4, Folder 70)
      - Julius Emspak to R.J. Hartley Regarding Constitution, January 8, 1937; 1.
      - Emspak to Frank Herdman Regarding Finances, January 13, 1937; 2.
      - Emspak to Hartley Regarding Rate Information, January 15, 1937; 3.
      - Emspak to Herdman Regarding Finances, February 17, 1937; 4.
      - Emspak to Hartley Regarding Charter, March 11, 1937; 5.
      - Emspak to E. Fillian Regarding Rate Information, March 25, 1937; 6.
      - Emspak to Hartley Regarding Staff Assignments, March 26, 1937; 7.
      - Emspak to Hartley Regarding Local Separation, March 29, 1937; 8.
      - Emspak to Hartley Regarding Local Organization, April 14, 1937; 9.
      - Emspak to Herdman Regarding Finances, April 17, 1937; 10.
      - Emspak to Hartley Regarding Publicity, April 19, 1937; 11.
      - Emspak to Herdman Regarding Supplies, June 21, 1937; 12.
      - Emspak to Alfred Yale Regarding Per Capita, August 25, 1937; 13.
      - Albert Stonkus to Hartley Regardng Meeting, June 28, 1937; 14.
      - Stonkus to Fillian Regarding Wage Rates, July 15, 1937; 15.
      - Stonkus to Hartley Regarding Materials, September 17, 1937; 16.
      - Stonkus to Yale Regarding Meeting, October 22, 1937; 17.
      - Stonkus to Yale Regarding Meeting, November 23, 1937; 18.
      - Stonkus to Hartley Regarding Negotiations, November 23, 1937; 19.
      - Stonkus to Yale Regarding Conference, November 14, 1937; 20.
      - Stonkus to Hartley Regarding Forwarded Letter, November 24, 1937; 21.
      - Stonkus to Hartley Regarding Conference Delegate, January 17, 1938; 22.
      - Stonkus to Yale Regarding Travel Plans, 23.
    - Local 704 (Cuyahoga Falls) Outgoing Correspondence, September 24, 1936-April 21, 1937 (Box 4, Folder 71)
      - W. Barringer to UE Regarding Supplies, September 24, 1936; 1.
      - Edward Fillian to UE Regarding Wage Rates, January 26, 1937; 2.
      - Fillian to Julius Emspak Regarding Wage Rates, March 18, 1937; 3.
      - Fillian to Emspak Regarding Wage Rates, June 25, 1937; 4.
      - R. Hartley to UE Regarding Mailing List, October 9, 1936; 5.
      - Hartley to UE Regarding Supplies, October 27, 1936; 6.
      - Hartley to Emspak Regarding Materials, November 9, 1936; 7.
      - Hartley to Emspak Regarding Address, November 11, 1936; 8.
      - Hartley to Emspak Regarding Materials, November 14, 1936; 9.
      - Hartley to Emspak Regarding Materials, November 25, 1936; 10.
      - Hartley to Emspak Regarding Materials, December 10, 1936; 11.
      - Hartley to Emspak Regarding Mailing List, December 22, 1936; 12.
      - Hartley to Emspak Regarding Wage Rates, December 28, 1936; 13.
      - Hartley to Emspak Regarding Constitution, December 29, 1936; 14.
      - Hartley to Emspak Regarding Membership List, January 12, 1937; 15.
      - Hartley to Emspak Regarding Wage Rates, January 12, 1937; 16.
      - Hartley to Emspak Regarding Local Organization, March 24, 1937; 17.
      - Hartley to Emspak Regarding Charter, March 27, 1937; 18.
      - Hartley to Emspak Regarding Local Organization, March 27, 1937; 19.
      - Hartley to Emspak Regarding Publicity, April 7, 1937; 20.
      - Hartley to Emspak Regarding Local Organization, April 13, 1937; 21.
      - Hartley to Emspak Regarding Convention, April 21, 1937; 22.
    - Local 704 (Cuyahoga Falls) Outgoing Correspondence, Ocober 12, 1936-February 8, 1938 (Box 4, Folder 72)
      - R. Hartley to Julius Emspak Regarding Address, May 26, 1937; 1.
      - Hartley to Emspak Regarding Information Request, June 22, 1937; 2.
      - Hartley to Albert Stonkus Regarding Local Delegates, August 18, 1937; 3.
      - Hartley to Stonkus Regarding Publications, September 14, 1937; 4.
      - Hartley to Stonkus Regarding Publications, August 18, 1937; 5.
      - Hartley to Emspak Regarding Meeting, September 14, 1937; 6.
      - Hartley to Stonkus Regarding Conference, January 13, 1938; 7.
      - Frank Herdman to UE Regarding Finances, October 12, 1936; 8.
      - Herdman to Emspak Regarding Finances, October 27, 1936; 9.
      - Herdman to Emspak Regarding Supplies, November 9, 1936; 10-11.
      - Herdman to Emspak Regarding Supplies, November 12, 1936; 12.
      - Herdman to Emspak Regarding Finances, November 16, 1936; 13.
      - Herdman to Emspak Regarding Finances and Supplies, December 18, 1936; 14.
      - Herdman to Emspak Regarding Supplies, January 8, 1937; 15.
      - Herdman to Emspak Regarding Finances, January 9, 1937; 16.
      - Herdman to Emspak Regarding Supplies, February 7, 1937; 17.
      - Herdman to Emspak Regarding Finances, April 13, 1937; 18.
      - Herdman to Emspak Regarding Supplies, November 3, 1937; 19.
      - Herdman to Emspak Regarding Supplies, November 21, 1937; 20.
      - Herdman to Emspak Regarding Finances, December 7, 1937; 21.
      - Herdman to Emspak Regarding Finances, February 8, 1938; 22.
      - Herdman to Emspak Regarding Supplies, 23-24.
    - Local 704 (Cuyahoga Falls) Financial Secretary Reports, November 1936-January 1938 (Box 4, Folder 73)
    - Local 704 (Cuyahoga Falls) Supply Requisitions, July 13-November 3, 1937 (Box 4, Folder 74)
    - Local 704 (Cuyahoga Falls) Salary and Expense Letters, July 21, 1937 (Box 4, Folder 75)
    - Local 704 (Cuyahoga Falls) Receipts, August 17, 1937-February 12, 1938 (Box 4, Folder 76)
    - Local 704 (Cuyahoga Falls) Correspondence, William Donovan to M.E. LeValley Regarding Ohio Edison Organization, September 4, 1936 (Box 4, Folder 77)
  - Local 704 (Bucyrus)
    - Local 704 (Bucyrus) Officer's List, March 1, 1944-September 1, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 78)
    - Local 704 (Bucyrus) Incoming Correspondence, October 19, 1945-February 12, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 79)
      - Janet Barish to Irene Van Gorden Regarding Finances, January 24, 1950; 1.
      - Julius Emspak to Virginia Rush Regarding Finances, October 19, 1945; 2.
      - Emspak to Robert Stewart Regarding Finances, December 26, 1945; 3.
      - Emspak to Rush Regarding Finances, March 25, 1946; 4.
      - Emspak to Rush Regarding Finances, January 17, 1947; 5.
      - Emspak to Van Gorden Regardng Finances, December 21, 1949; 6.
      - Emspak to Van Gorden Regarding Strike Finances, March 8, 1950; 7.
      - Emspak to Emma Mullins Regarding Finances, May 5, 1950; 8.
      - Emspak to Van Gorden Regarding Finances, August 28, 1950; 9.
      - Emspak to Van Gorden Regarding Finances, October 26, 1950; 10.
      - Emspak to Doyle Walimire Regarding Finances, December 13, 1950; 11.
      - Emspak to Walimire Regarding Finances, January 31, 1951; 12.
      - Emspak to Walimire Regarding Charter, February 12, 1951; 13.
    - Local 704 (Bucyrus) Outgoing Correspondence, February 10, 1944-December 12, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 80)
      - Russell Dutcher to Julius Emspak Regarding Financial Report, February 10, 1944; 1.
      - H.W. Diehl to UE Regarding Finances, August 22, 1947; 2.
      - P. Funk to UE Regarding Finances, September 13, 1948; 3.
      - Rosemary King to Janet Barish Regarding Mailing List, January 18, 1949; 4.
      - King to Emspak Regarding Address, December 12, 1950; 5.
      - M. Patterson to UE Regarding Finances, August 25, 1947; 6.
      - Patterson to UE Regarding Finances, July 31, 1948; 7.
      - Patterson to UE Regarding Finances, September 20, 1948; 8.
      - Virginia Rush to Joe Dermody Regarding Finances, March 18, 1946; 9.
      - Rush to Emspak Regarding Contract, July11, 1946; 10.
      - Rush to Emspak Regarding Finances, January 22, 1947; 11.
      - Edward Uhl to Emspak Regarding Finances, 12.
      - Van Gorden to Emspak Regarding Finances, March 10, 1950; 13.
      - Doyle Walimire to Emspak Regarding Finances, December 5, 1950; 14.
      - Betty Waters to Emspak Regarding Credentials, August 31, 1948; 15.
    - Local 704 (Bucyrus) Financial Secretary Statements (Box 4, Folder 81)
    - Local 704 (Bucyrus) Money Orders, October 28, 1949-March 8, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 82)
    - Local 704 (Bucyrus) Organization, December 28, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 83)
      - Julius Emspak to Victor Decavitch, December 28, 1943; 1.
      - Emspak to Steve Thoma, December 28, 1943; 2.
    - Local 704 (Bucyrus) International Association of Machinists Inter-union Rivalry, January 23-February 1, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 84)
      - IAM National Labor Relations Board Brief, 1.
      - Michael Essin to James Matles, January 23, 1958; 2.
      - Essin to NLRB, January 30, 1958; 3.
      - UE NLRB Brief, January 30, 1958; 4.
      - Ogden Fields NLBR Order, February 5, 1958; 5.
      - Essin to Matles, February 7, 1958; 6.
      - Robert Simpson to Walter Schlotterback, February 7, 1958; 7.
      - Essin to Matles, February 17, 1958; 8.
      - Essin to Edward Grupp, February 17, 1958; 9.
      - Essn to Grupp, February 19, 1958; 10.
    - Local 704 (Bucyrus) Correspondence and Reports, February 21, 1944-April 1, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 85)
      - Julius Emspak to Steve Thoma Regarding Local 704 Organization, February 21, 1944; 1.
      - Victor Decavitch to Joseph Dermody Regarding Local 704 Officers, May 8, 1944; 2.
      - Report of Strike, January 15, 1946; 3.
      - Memo to Janet Regarding Finances and Inter-union Rivalry, December 8, 1950; 4.
      - Rosemary King to Julius Emspak Regarding Finances and IUE Inter-union Rivalry, January 29, 1951; 5.
      - King to Emspak Regarding Officers, January 14, 1954; 6.
      - Paul Dunham to James Matles Regarding Membership, January 25, 1956; 7.
      - J.F. Kebe to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Women's Wages, APril 1, 1957; 8.
  - Local 705
    - Local 705 Officers List, 1944-1950 (Box 4, Folder 86)
    - Local 705 Constitution, October 23, 1943-December 29, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 87)
    - Local 705 Incoming Correspondence, September 21, 1939-March 17, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 88)
      - Julius Emspak to Otto Lommatzsch Regarding Supplies, September 21, 1939; 1.
      - Emspak to D. Antram Regarding Bonding, October 12, 1943; 2.
      - Emspak to Donald Haidet Regarding Finances, February 28, 1945; 3.
      - Emspak to Kathryn Stewart Regarding Charter, April 14, 1948; 4.
      - Emspak to Ernest Hooper Regarding Bonding, May 24, 1950; 5.
      - Emspak to Paul Burgress Regarding Strike Finances, March 17, 1952; 6.
      - Albert Fitzgerald to Burgress Regarding Negotiatons, February 14, 1951; 7.
      - Unsigned Letter to Antram Regarding Publications, February 7, 1944; 8.
    - Local 705 Outgoing Correspondence, January 26, 1944-March 9, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 89)
      - Donald Antram to UE Regarding Publication, January 26, 1944; 1.
      - Antram to Julius Emspak Regarding Finances, August 23, 1944; 2.
      - Paul Burgress to UE Regarding Charter, November 21, 1947; 3.
      - Burgress to Emspak Regarding Lockout, March 9, 1952; 4.
      - Donald Haidet to UE Regarding Membership, February 20, 1945; 5.
      - Ernest Hooper to Emspak Regarding Negotiations, April 14, 1950; 6.
      - Hooper to Emspak Regarding Finances, May 21, 1950; 7.
      - Hooper to Emspak Regarding Officer, October 3, 1950; 8.
      - Karl Johnson to James Matles Regarding Election, February 28, 1950; 9.
      - Louise McPeak to UE Regarding Finances, April 19, 1952; 10.
      - Katherine Molnar to UE Regarding Negotiations, February 26, 1944; 11.
      - Joseph Nagy to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Lockout, February 27, 1951; 12.
      - Kathryn Stewart to UE Regarding Charter, April 10, 1948; 13.
      - Stewart to Emspak Regarding Finances, October 25, 1949; 14.
      - Resolution, 15.
      - Local 705 to UE Regardng Negotiations, February 6, 1950; 16.
    - Local 705 Per Capita, August 14, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 90)
    - Local 705 Organization, September 18-October 13, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 91)
      - Leo Turner to Julius Emspak, September 18, 1943; 1.
      - Emspak to Turner, December 8, 1943; 2.
      - Emspak to Victor Decavitch, October 13, 1943; 3.
    - Local 705 Per Capita, December 6-17, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 92)
      - Julius Emspak to Herbert Hirshberg, December 6, 1948; 1.
      - Hirshberg to Emspak, December 8, 1948; 2.
      - Jake Staas to Emspak, December 17, 1948; 3.
    - Local 705 Correspondence, February 12, 1946-January 30, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 93)
      - Paul Duham to James Matles Regarding Wages, February12, 1946; 1.
      - Julius Emspak to Lem Markland Regarding Charter Expansion, November 24, 1947; 2.
      - Herbert Hirshberg to Emspak Regarding Factionalism, October 5, 1950; 3.
      - Victor Pasche to Emspak Regarding Per Capita, January 30, 1951; 4.
    - Loca 705 Correspondence, February 14, 1975-August 2, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 94)
    - Local 705 Mansfield Ideal Electric, September 28, 1936-August 22, 1938 (Box 4, Folder 95)
    - Local 705 Mansfield Ideal Electric, September 16, 1936-November 8, 1937 (Box 4, Folder 96)
  - Local 706
    - Local 706 Officers List, January 13-December 23, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 97)
    - Local 706 Constitution, January 11-September 6, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 98)
    - Local 706 Incoming Correspondence, March 29, 1943-February 23, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 99)
      - Julius Emspak to Frank McIntosh Regarding Charter, March 29, 1943; 1.
      - Emspak to McIntosh Regarding Bonding, March 29, 1943; 2.
      - Emspak to M. Colling Regarding Finances, February 23, 1945; 3.
      - Albert Fitzgerald to Mary Newell Regarding Bonding, May 8, 1944; 4.
      - Fitzgerald to Newell Regarding Constitution, May 19, 1944; 5.
      - Fredrick Livingston to Newell Regarding Wage Payment, April 25, 1944; 6.
      - Edward Matthews to Ella Garner Regarding Finances, November 3, 1943; 7.
      - A. Towsen to Newell Regarding Finances, April 19, 1944; 8.
    - Local 706 Outgoing Correspondence, June 5, 1943-February 14, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 100)
      - M. Collins to Julius Emspak Regarding Finances, February 14, 1945; 1.
      - James Dickson Letter Regarding Officers, June 5, 1943; 2.
      - Thomas Finnerty to Emspak Regarding Constitution, December 27, 1943; 3.
      - Finnerty to Emspak Regarding Finances, December 27, 1943; 4.
      - Finnerty to Emspak Regarding Contract, February 1, 1944; 5.
      - Finnerty to Victor Decavitch Regarding Constitution, August 14, 1944; 6.
      - Ella Garner to Emspak Regarding Finances, October 13, 1943; 7.
      - Mary Newell to Dave Ratner Regarding Finances, April 10, 1944; 8.
      - Newell to Herbert Wright Regarding Declared Changes, April 18, 1944; 9.
      - Newell to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Bonding, May 3, 1944; 10.
      - Newell to Fitzgerald Regarding Membership, May 3, 1944; 11.
      - Newell to J. Nuth Regarding Membership, May 3, 1944; 12.